HELMI AGUSTIAWAN

FRONT END WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT



Profile

My name is Helmi Agustiawan and I am 22 years old, I graduated from Gunadarma University majoring in information systems. I have a good health condition. Besides communicating well and politely, i can also work as a team or individually. every job is always done in detail and on time. I believe I can contribute to this work

Interests



CODING

I Love coding website

Experience

2018 - 2019 Gunadarma University

Teaching Assistant Laboratorium Inform

ation System, city

I served as a teaching assistant to teach

about programming material

2020 - Present Badan Kepegawaian Negara

Front End Web Development, city Works as a front-end developer with the task of slicing a website design from an ui designer into a website page

Skills

Skill group

HTML CSS BOOTSTRAP SASS REACT JS JAVASCRIPT



Education

2013 - 2016 Senior High School / SMAN 22 Jakarta

Student. East Jakarta

Description of the education/course.

2016 - 2020 Gunadarma University

Information System, Depok

Description of the education/course.

Contact

- Bogor
- 081319982858
- in helmi agustiawan
- f helmi agustiawan
- velvas45